Guide to the Stanford University, W. W. Hansen Laboratories of Physics, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, W. W. Hansen Laboratories of Physics, records
1947-1964
SC0062
Stanford University. W.W. Hansen Laboratory of Physics.
15 Linear feet
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Transferred by the W. W. Hansen Laboratories, 1969
Information about Access
None.
Scope and Contents
Contracts, proposals, correspondence, and memoranda from the files of the William W. Hansen Laboratories relating to the construction of the Stanford Linear Accelerator, the development of the Klystron tube, and medical research using linear accelerators.
Collection Contents
- CONSTRUCTION OF A LINEAR ELECTRON ACCELERATOR
  - Construction of a Linear Electron Accelerator, (N6ori 106 Task order IV), 12-Jun-46 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- AN INVESTIGATION OF HIGH POWER PULSED KLYSTRONS
  - An Investigation of High Power Pulsed Klystrons Including Studies of the Problems Connected With the Design of 100 Megawatt 10 cm Klystrons (N6onr 251 Task order IX), June 1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- TO DESIGN, DEVELOP AND CONSTRUCT A LINEAR ELECTRON ACCELERATOR SUITABLE FOR NUCLEAR RESEARCH
  - Master Contract, (N6onr 25116), June 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - General correspondence, (N6onr 25116), September 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Memos: General Plans to ONR, (N6onr 25116), July 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Patent Certificates, (N6onr 25116), May 1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Contract Cutback, (N6onr 25116), May 1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Non-Servable Property, (N6onr 25116), February 1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Graphs, (N6onr 25116), May 1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Final Report, (N6onr 25116), April 1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Carl N. Swenson - Construction of Addition to HEPL End Station, (N6onr 25116), July 1962 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Spencer and Lee - HEPL End Station Extension, (N6onr 25116), February 1962 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Spencer and Lee - HEPL End Station Extension, (N6onr 25116), February 1962 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Princeton - General Correspondence, (N6onr 25116), January 1959 to November 1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Princeton - 5th Amendment - Funding for Calendar Year 1962, (N6onr 25116), December 1961 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Princeton - 4th Amendment to Subcontract, (N6onr 25116), August 1961 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Princeton - 3rd Amendment Covering Application Staff Benefits, (N6onr 25116), January 1959 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Princeton - 2nd Amendment - (N6onr 25116), January 1, 1961 to December 31, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Amendment to Subcontract - (N6onr 25116), January 1, 1960 to December 31, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Princeton Subcontract - Extra Copies, (N6onr 25116), January 1959 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Princeton Subcontract - Princeton Billing, (N6onr 25116), March 1959 to January 1963 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Princeton Subcontract Property Reconrds, (N6onr 25116), May 1959 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Princeton Subcontract - Dittos and Worksheets, (N6onr 25116), January 1959 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Princeton - Final Property Accounting, (N6onr 25116), March 1963 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Subcontract with Schlegel Plumbing - Recirculating Cooling Water System, (N6onr 25116), November 1959 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Fabrication of Electrical Coils for 6 Storage Ring Magnets - Spectromagnetic Industries, (N6onr 25116), June 1959 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Modification of a 36 and 72 Magnetic Spectrometer Mount - Triple A Machine Shop, (N6onr 25116), May 1959 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Fabrication of Storage Ring Magnet Steel Shells - Bethlehem Pacific Coast Steel Co., (N6onr 25116), June 1959 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Worksheets and Dittos - Storage Ring Magnetic Shells, (N6onr 25116), June 1959 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Cortelyou and Cole Inc. - Radiation Shielding for the Mark III Accelerator 90 foot Extension, (N6onr 25116), May 1959 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Williams and Burrows Subcontractors - Colliding-Beam Vault, (N6onr 25116), February 1959 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Spencer and Lee Subcontractors - Colliding-Beam Vault Design, (N6onr 25116), February 1959 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Williams and Burrows - 72 Magnetic Spectrometer House, (N6onr 25116), February 1959 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Spencer and Lee - 72 Spectrometer Generator, House, (N6onr 25116), February 1959 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Wells P. Goodenough - Mark III Control Room, (N6onr 25116), August 1958 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Wells P. Goodenough Inc. - 72 Magnetic Spectrometer Mount Rail Support and Utility Trench, (N6onr 25116), November 1958 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Baldwin-Lima-Hamilton Corp. - 72 Spectrometer Magnet Frames and Vacuum Chamber, (N6onr 25116), June 1958, October 1958 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - National Electric Coil Co. - 72 Spectrometer Magnet, Main and Auxilary Coils, (N6onr 25116), June 1958 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - National Electric Co. - 72 Magnet-Coils Shipment and Damage Claims, (N6onr 25116), 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Photographs and Nec. Time Records - 72 Magnetic Spectrometer Damage, (N6onr 25116), July 1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Houseman Construction Co. - Meson Spectrometer Pit, (N6onr 25116), 1957 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Houseman Construction Co. - Enc Station Exterior Shielding, (N6onr 25116), 1957 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Houseman Construction Co. - Power Vault, (N6onr 25116), March 1956 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Spencer and Ambrose - Power Vault, (N6onr 25116), March 1955 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - P. J. Ranch Co., (N6onr 25116), November 1953 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Rothschild, Raffin, and Weirick, (N6onr 25116), June 1953 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Spencer and Ambrose - Sheilding, (N6onr 25116), March 1953 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Extension Proposal for Research and Operations and Colliding Beams - Experiment 1964 - Plus Special Budgets, (N6onr 25116), September 1962 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Extension Proposal for Research and Operations and Colliding Beams - Experiment CY 1964 - Plus Special Budgets (Dittos and Worksheets), (N6onr 25116), September 1962 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Extension Proposal for Research and Operations CY 1963 - Colliding Beams - Experiment CY 1962 and 1963, (N6onr 25116), October 1961 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Extension Proposal for Research and Operations CY 1963 - Colliding Beams - Experiment CY 1962 1963 - Extra Copies and Ditto Masters, (N6onr 25116), October 1961 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - 72 - 180 degree Mass Magnetic Spectrometer Costs (N6onr 25116), September 1961 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Colliding Beams Experiment - Informal Letter to W.E. Wright, (N6onr 25116), July 1961 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Construction of target Vault, etc. - Ditto Masters and Extra Copies, (N6onr 25116), June 1961 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Construction of Target Vault, Spectrometer, Model of Accelerator and Improvement of Experimental Possibilities, (N6onr 25116), June 1961 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Construction of Target Area Vault for the Mark III Linear Electron Accelerator, (N6onr 25116), December 1960 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Extension Propsal for Contract N6onr 25116 - Worksheets, Dittos, Extra Copies - Dr. Panofsky, (N6onr 25116), November 1960 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Extension Proposal - Dr. Panofsky - Dr. Hofstadter, (N6onr 25116), November 1960 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Extension Proposal - Dr. Panofsky - Dr. Hofstadter, (N6onr 25116), July 1959 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Extension Proposal - Worksheets, Dittos, Extra Copies, (N6onr 25116), July 1959 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Extension Proposal - Increase in Cost, (N6onr 25116), August 1958 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Extension Proposal - Worksheets, Dittos, Extra Pages, (N6onr 25116), August 1958 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Colliding Beam Proposal, (N6onr 25116), May 1958 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Proposal for Mark III 80 foot Extension - Work Papers and Ditto Masters, (N6onr 25116), January 1958 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Proposal to ONR for Extension of Contract - Ditto Masters and Extra Copies, (N6onr 25116), November 1957 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Proposal - Worksheets and Draft, (N6onr 25116), November 1957 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Extension Proposal - Dittoo Masters and Extra Copies, (N6onr 25116), January 1957 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Extension Proposal with Increase in Estimated Cost, (N6onr 25116), August 1956 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Extension Proposal - Ditto Masters and Extra Copies, (N6onr 25116), August 1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Extension Proposal for Indefinite Period (N6onr 25116), February 1956 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Extension Proposal for Indefinite Period - Extra Copies and Dittos, (N6onr 25116), February 1956 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Extension Proposal for One Year Beginning December 1, 1955, to December 1, 1956, (N6onr 25116) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Extension Proposal for One Year Beginning April 1, 1955 - March 31, 1956, (N6onr 25116), November 1953 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Amended Proposal - December 1, 1954 - December 1, 1956, (N6onr 25116), February 1955 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Proposal for Budget Extension - August 1, 1954 - March 15, 1955, (N6onr 25116), May 1953 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Extension Proposal - August 1, 1953 - July 31, 1954, (N6onr 25116), December 1952 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Proposal for Expedite Showers - AFSWP - November 1952, (N6onr 25116), April 1953 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Extension Proposal - April 1, 1952 - September 30, 1953, (N6onr 25116), February 1951 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Proposal to Procur End Station Equipment and Shielding, (N6onr 25116), December 1952 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Memo: Procurement of End Station Equipment and Shielding - October 1, 1952 (N6onr 25116) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Extension Proposal - August 1, 1952 - July 31, 1953, (N6onr 25116), January 1952 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Proposal to Procure End Station Equipment and Shielding, (N6onr 25116), May 1952 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Extension Proposal - August 1, 1951 - March 31, 1952, (N6onr 25116), February 1951 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Proposal Requesting Additional Funds - June 1, 1951 - May 31, 1952, (N6onr 25116), May 1951 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Contract and Amendments - Extra Copies, (N6onr 25116), June 1948 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Physics - Research Proposal, (N6onr 25116), December 1950 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Proposed Extension Budget - August 1, 1950 - June 30, 1951 (N6onr 25116) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Extension Proposal - July 25, 1950 - July 31, 1952 (N6onr 25116), April 1950 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - REV Accelerator Proposal, (N6onr 25116), April 1948 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Proposal - March 1, 1948 (N6onr 25116) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Task 16 - 1961 Operating Budgets, (N6onr 25116), November 1960 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Task 16 - 1960 Operating Budgets, (N6onr 25116) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Task 16 - 1957 Operating Budgets, (N6onr 25116), June 1953 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Revision of Budget for Calendar Year 1963, (N6onr 25116), May 1962 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Task 16 - 1962 Operating Budgets, (n6onr 25116) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Task 16 - 1955-1956 Operating Budgets, (N6onr 25116) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Task 16 - Reconciliation Notes on Closeout and Fund Transfer to 67, (N6onr 25116), January 1964 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Analysis of Research Costs 1953-1962 Prepared for Use by ONR Washington, (N6onr 25116), May 1963 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Adequate Budget to ONR - April 12, 1955, (N6onr 25116), April 1954 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Budget Control 1953 - 1954 (N6onr 25116) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Budget Control 1952 - 1953 (N6onr 25116) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Budget Control August 1, 1951 - January 31, 1953 (N6onr 25116) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Budget Memoranda 1948 - 1949, (N6onr 25116) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Inventory of Property as of December 31, 1962, (N6onr 25116), April 1964 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Transfer of GFE from the Final Property Accounting of Contract AT (04-3)-21, P.A. 2, (N6onr 25116), September 1961 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory, (N6onr 25116), June 1957 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory, (N6onr 25116), June 1957 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory, (N6onr 25116), June 1956 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory (Extra Copies), (n6onr 25116), June 1956 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Interim Annual Inventory 1954 - 1955. Correspondence, Memos, etc. (N6onr 25116) (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Interim Physical Inventory, (N6onr 25116), April 1955 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Property Transfers from ERL, (N6onr 25116), February 1961 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Property Transferred from Final Inventory of Contract AF 18 (600)-646, (N6onr 251160), April 1948 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Final Property Accounting as of December 31, 1962, (N6onr 25116), May 1964 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- INVESTIGATION OF MICROWAVE NOISE SOURCES
  - Contract, (N6onr 25116), March 1949 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, (N6onr 25116), March 1949 - March 1950 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Original Proposal, (N6onr 25116), December 1948 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Termination, (N6onr 25116), September 1950 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Contract and Amendments, (N6onr 25123), April 1950 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - General, (N6onr 25123), February 1950 - February 1964 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Patent Certificates, (N6onr 25123), May 1956 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Extension Proposal - November 1958 (N6onr 25123) (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Proposal to ONR for Increase Support for Contract N6onr 25123 - May 1958 - $100,000 (N6onr 25123) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Proposal to ONR for Additional Support for Investigation of High-Power Microwave Devices, (N6onr 25123), May 1958 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Revised Proposal for High-Power Pulsed Klystron Work, (N6onr 25123), April 1958 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Proposal to ONR for Additional Support for the Investigation of High-Power Microwave Devices, (N6onr 25123), February 1958 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Proposal for High-Power Pulsed Klystron Work (N6onr 25123), January 1958 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Proposal for Extension During 1959, (N6onr 25123), January 1958 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Extension Proposal - January 1, 1958 to December 31, 1958, (N6onr 25123), December 1956 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Extension Proposal - January 1, 1957 to December 31, 1957, (N6onr 25123), October 1955 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Extension Proposal - January 1, 1956 to December 31, 1956 - Also Increase in '55 Rate, (N6onr 25123), August 1954 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Extension Proposal - January 1, 1955 to December 31, 1955, (N6onr 25123), November 1953 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Budget Control, (N6onr 25123), January 1954 - August 1954 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Extension Proposal - December 15, 1953 to December 15, 1854, (N6onr 25123), March 1953 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Extension Proposal - November 1, 1952 to October 31, 1953, (N6onr 25123), October 1951 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Extension Proposal - November 1, 1951 to October 31, 1952, (N6onr 25123), February 1951 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Proposal for Research on Generation of mm. Waves, (N6onr 25123), July 1952 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Original Proposal, (N6onr 25123), January 1951 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Interim Physical Inventory, (N6onr 25123), April 1955 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory, (N6onr 25123), June 1956 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory, (N6onr 25123), June 1957 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Transfer of Final Inventory from Contract Nonr 225 (05), (N6onr 25123), October 1956 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Final Inventory, (N6onr 25123), March 1960 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Transfer of Final Inventory from Contract Nonr 225 (06), (N6onr 25123), January 1959 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Transfer of Final Inventory from Contract Nonr 225 (26), (N6onr 25123), January 1959 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Final Property Accounting, (N6onr 25123), March 1960 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- TO DESIGN, DEVELOP AND CONSTRUCT A KLYSTRON TUBE WHICH COULD EASILY BE REPRODUCED BY A MANUFACTURER WITHOUT REPEATING THE DESIGN, DEVELOPMENT AND DRAFTING EFFORT; AND TO MANUFACTURE TEM PROTOTYPE KLYSTRON TUBES, BASED ON THE DESIGN REFERRED TO ABOVE, FOR DELIVERY TO THE BUREAU OF SHIPS
  - Contract, Amendments and Briefs, (Nonr 225 (05)), March 1952 - March 1958 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, (Nonr 225 (05)), January 1952 - May 1958 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Extension Proposal, (Nonr 225 (05), August 1954 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Extension Proposal, (Nonr 225 (05)), July 1953 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Extension Proposal, (Nonr 225 (05)), June 1953 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Proposal of 1951 - original, (Nonr 225 (05)), August 1951 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Subcontracted Machine Work, (Nonr 225 (05)), 1954 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Litton Subcontracts and Amendments, (Nonr 225 (05)), October 1953 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Litton Correspondence, March 1952 - March 1955 and Litton Subcontract Invoices, (Nonr 225 (05)), March 1953 - August 1954 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Litton Industries Subcontract S110 - Tube Shipments, (Nonr 225 (05)), October 1955 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Tube Shipments, (Nonr 225 (05)), October 1954 - March 1955 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Klystron Cost Estimate, (Nonr 225 (05)), November 1958 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Security Information, (Nonr 225 (05)), August 1957 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Patent Certificates, (Nonr 225 (05)), May 1956 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Physical Interim Inventory, (Nonr 225 (05)), May 1955 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Final Property Accounting - Office of Naval Research, (Nonr 225 (05)), February 1957 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- DEVELOPMENT OF 6 MEV LINEAR ACCELERATOR FOR MEDICAL AND RADIOGRAPHICAL APPLICATIONS
  - Contract and Amendments, (Nonr 225 (06)), March 1952 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence, (Nonr 225 (06)), March 1953 - June 1958 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Extension Proposal for Nine Months - beginning September 1, 1957, (Nonr 225 (06)), August 1957 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Extention Proposal for One Year - beginning September 1, 1956, (Nonr 225 (06)), May 1956 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Extension Proposal for September 1, 1955 through August 31, 1956, (Nonr 225 (06)), May 1955 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Extension Proposal for June 1, 1954 through May 31, 1955, (Nonr 225 (06)), December 1953 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Extension Proposal for Two Years from June 1, 1953 through May 31, 1955, (Nonr 225 (06)), February 1953 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Original Proposal, (Nonr 225 (06)), December 1951 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Patent Certificates, (Nonr 225 (06)), May 1956 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory, (Nonr 225 (06)), June 1957 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory, (Nonr 225 (06)), June 1956 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Interim Physical Inventory, (Nonr 225 (06)), May 1955 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Final Property Accounting, (Nonr 225 (06)), October 1958 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- X-BAND KLYSTRON FOR WRIGHT FIELD
  - Contract, (Nonr 225 (12)), May 1952 - May 1954 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- BASIC STUDIES IN FERROELECTRICITY
  - Contract and Amendments, (Nonr 225 (18)), November 1954 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, (Nonr 225 (18)), March 1955 - December 1958 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Extension Proposal for November 1, 1957 through October 31, 1958, (Nonr 225 (18)), August 1957 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Extension Proposal for November 1, 1956 through October 31, 1957, (Nonr 225 (18)), July 1956 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Extension Proposal for November 1, 1955 through October 31, 1956, (Nonr 225 (18)), October 1955 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Original Proposal (Revised Budget), (Nonr 225 (18)), May 1954 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Patent Certificates, (Nonr 225 (18)), May 1956 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory, (Nonr 225 (18)), June 1956 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory, (Nonr 225 (18)), April 1955 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Final Property Accounting, (Nonr 225 (18)), March 1959 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- AN INVESTIGATION OF HIGH-POWER MICROWAVE DEVICES
  - Contract and Amendments, (Nonr 225 (26)), June 1956 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, (Nonr 225 (26)), June 1958 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Proposal to Extend Investigation of High-Power Microwave Devices, (Nonr 225 (26)), April 1958 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Extension Proposal for May 31, 1957 through May 31, 1958, (Nonr 225 (26)), March 1957 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Original Proposal (Originally a Task 23 Proposal), (Nonr 225 (26)), February 1956 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Patents, (Nonr 225 (26)), August 1958 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Initial Interim Annual Physical Inventory, (Nonr 225 (26)), June 1957 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Final Property Accounting, (Nonr 225 (26)), November 1958 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- LINCOLN PROJECT
  - Lincoln Project, (N6onr 25132L), 1952 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- CONSOLIDATED ELECTRONICS: FINANCIAL HISTORY
  - Consolidated Electronics: Financial History (Ginzton), (N6onr 251 Task Order 7M), August 1954 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- PARTIAL SUPPORT OF THE THIRD INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM ON X-RAY OPTICS AND X-RAY MICROANALYSIS
  - Partial Support of the Symposium on X-Ray Optics and X-Ray Microananlysis from March 1, 1962 through February 28, 1963, (Nonr (G)-00062-62), December 1961 - April 1963 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- SUPPORT OF A SYMPOSIUM ON THE QUANTUM ASPECTS OF POLYPEPTIDES AND POLYNUCLEOTIDES
  - Symposium on the Quantum Aspects of Polypeptides and Polynucleotides, (Nonr (G)-0007-63), May 1962 - April 1964 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- RESEARCH ON GENERATION OF MILLIMETER-WAVELENGTH ELECTRO-MAGNETIC WAVES
  - Contract, October 1952 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Proposals and Correspondence, (Nonr 1045 (00)), June 1952 - November 1955 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- AN INVESTIGATION OF CAVITY ANTENNAS
  - Contract, (AF W 28-099 ac-382), January 1948 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, (AF W 28-099 ac-382), June 1947 - January 1950 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Proposed Continuation, (AF W 28-099 ac-382), 1949 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Original Proposal, (AF W 28-099 ac-382), 1947 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Watson Laboratory, (AF W 28-099 ac-382), November 1949 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Termination, (AF W 28-099 ac-382), August 1949 - February 1950 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- THEORETICAL AND EXPERIMENTAL INVESTIGATION OF CAVITY ANTENNAS
  - Contract, (AF 19 (122-41)), November 1949 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, (AF 19 (122-41)), January 1947 - February 1950 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Proposals, (AF 19 (122-41)), 1950 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - M.I.T. Subcontract No. 33 - Miscellaneous, (AF 19 (122-41)), April 1954 - July 1957 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Termination, (AF 19 (122-41)), December 1950 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- RESEARCH ON ELECTRON SCATTERING AND NUCLEAR STRUCTURE
  - Contract and Amendments, (AF 18 (600)-646), March 1953 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence, (AF 18 (600)-646), May 1953 - November 1961 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Extension Proposal for December 31, 1956 through April 30, 1956, (AF 18 (600)-646), November 1956 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Extension Proposa with Increase in Rate for November 1, 1955 through December 31, 1956, (AF 18 (600)-646), August 1955 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Extension Proposal for October 1, 1955 through September 30, 1956, (AF 18 (600)-646), December 1954 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Extension Proposal for May 1, 1954 through September 30, 1955, (AF 18 (600)-646), August 1953 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Proposal, (AF 18 (600)-646), August 1952 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Supplement #4, Extension of this Contract - Requirements, Outline of Reports, etc., (AF 18 (600)-646), July 1955 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Reports Distribution, (AF 18 (600)-646), July 1955 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Budget, (AF 18 (600)-646), August 1955 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Property Instuctions, etc., (AF 18 (600)-646), July 1954 - March 1957 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Interim Annual Physical Inventory, (AF 18 (600)-646), June 1956 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Interim Physical Inventory, (AF 18 (600)-646), May 1955 (Box 15, Folder 11)